# Timilehin Adepoju

Digital Product Designer

Lagos, Nigeria +2349079133294, +2349121573118 adepojutimilehin7@gmail.com

# **Summary**

A seasoned digital product designer with a patented design approach to user experience design who is confident in accepting challenges. I am highly skilled in solving complex problems with creative thinking to provide deliberate solutions that brings high commercial value.

# **Work Experience**

## **Product Design Fellow**

Jan. 2022 - Present

#### The Bulb Africa

- Worked closely with other fellows to create user centric, pixel-perfect and accessible user experiences on the inhouse projects.
- Led the design for the product design track first project.
  A mobile application that allows people buy quality
  second hand clothes from the comfort of their home.
- Designed an examination portal interface for subsequent cohorts coming into the fellowship program.
- Conducted user research, created user flows, came up with personas, wireframes and presented a case study.
- Delivered on projects and assignments and was championed fellow of the month for the month of April.

#### Freelance Designer

Oct. 2021 - Jan. 2022

#### Independent

- Redesigned the onboarding process and homepage of Vbank mobile application in order to help improve the user experience.
- Designed a mobile application that promotes and encourage tourism within the country (Nigeria) as my capstone project.
- Conducted user research, created user flow, created low-fi and hi-fi wireframes and presented a case study.

# **Education**

The Bulb Africa Fellowship

**Product Design Training** 

Jan. 2022 - Present

Ovalay Academy

**UX/UI Design Training** 

July 2021 - Dec. 2021

Federal University Oye-Ekiti

B. Eng. Agricultural Engineering

Jan. 2013 - Jan. 2019

# Certification

**Ovalay Academy** 

UX/UI: How to design mobile apps and website from ground up.

December 2021.

### **Skills**

- · UX Design
- UI Design
- · User Researching
- Prototyping
- Task Flow
- · Wireframing
- · Excellent Communication Skills
- · Team Player
- Time Management

# **Tools**

- Figma
- · Figjam
- · Whimsical

# **Achievements & Awards**

Best Graduating student 2018/2019 session, Agricultural Engineering Dept.